ANDRÉS MAURICIO TRIANA REINA

SYSTEMS ENGINEER
DATA ANALYTICS
DATA VISUALITATIONS
MONITORING AND EVALUATION

+(57) 3108669185

@andresmtr



andrestrianareina@outlook.com



linkedin.com/in/andres-mauricio-triana-reina/



andrestrianareina.pythonanywhere.com



SKILLS AND TOOLS

OFFICE EXCEL

WORD POWER POINT

DATA COLLECTION

GOOGLE FORMS KOBOTOOLBOX

CODING

JUPYTER NOTEBOOK VISUAL STUDIO CODE GOOGLE COLABORATORY

DATA ANALYTICS AND VISUALIZATION

PYTHON
PANDAS
NUMPY
SEABORN
MATPLOTLIB
PLOTLY
CHART JS
SQL
DATA STUDIO
POWER BI
DASH - PLOTLY

BEAUTIFUL SOUP - WEB SCRAPING

WEB DEVELOPMENT

HTML
CSS
BOOTSTRAP
JAVASCRIPT
PYTHON
DJANGO
SOL

PROJECT MANAGEMENT

SLACK TRELLO MICROSOFT TEAMS

SOFT SKILLS

PROBLEM SOLVING CRITICAL THINKING COMMUNICATION TEAMWORK CREATIVITY

LANGUAGES

SPANISH - NATIVE ENGLISH - B2

PROFILE

Systems engineer with extensive experience in positions such as database management, evaluation and monitoring, construction of management reports and progress indicators, using Python and Excel for extraction, debugging, analysis, visualization of data and information. Strengths in interpreting, analyzing and diagnosing process advances, good at designing and implementing operational plans oriented to timely decision–making.

EXPERIENCE

(2021 - currently employed)

IMMAP

Data Analyst Expert

Compile, debug, process and analytic information from different sources, primary and secondary, using new technologies for processing and analysis of data, artificial intelligence, programming languages and data mining to improve the quality of information about products.

PYTHON DJANGO PANDAS WEB SCRAPING KOBOTOOLBOX DATA STUDIO POWER BI EXCEL WORD

(2018 - 2021)

IOM - INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATION FOR MIGRATION

Professional system information

Manage databases and update report indicators, guaranteeing quality and consistency of information, supporting consolidation of information for internal and external reports.

PYTHON KOBOTOOLBOX EXCEL WORD POWER POINT

(2017 - 2018)

ASOCIACIÓN COLOMBIANA DE DISTRIBUIDORES PELÍCULAS CINEMATOGRÁFICAS

Manage databases - Cadbox

Manage databases of movie tickets sold in Colombia and update the information in the CADBOX app. In addition, manage users in the system and create reports for associates. **EXCEL SQL**

(2013 - 2017)

FUPAD/FUCOLDE

Data analyst / Evaluation and monitoring

Manage, creation and depuration of databases with the purpose to build information, reports and indicators.

EXCEL WORD POWER POINT GOOGLE FORMS

EDUCATION

(2017 - 2020)

Systems engineer

UNAD - UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL ABIERTA Y A DISTANCIA.

(2014 - 2016)

Technology in analysis and development of information systems

SENA - SERVICIO NACIONAL DE APRENDIZAJE

COURSES/CERTIFICATIONS

Comprehensive SQL Bootcamp : Beginner to Advanced - Udemy SQL course - Sololearn

Interactive Python Dashboards with Plotly and Dash - Udemy

Python for Data Sciences and machine learning Bootcamp - Udemy

Big Data Analytics: Opportunities, Challenges and the future - Future Learn

Google Curso de introducción al desarrollo web: HTML y CSS - Google activate

Python course - Sololearn